Frances Benjamin Johnston Collection, 1935-1938 P0006
Frances Benjamin Johnston Collection, 1935-1938
- Frances Benjamin Johnston Collection, 1935-1938., Items: 2,280 images. Approximately 3.57 Linear Feet. Nine document boxes and five drawers in map case.
  - Gaston County: Dallas: Town Hall (Old Courthouse), circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 2 images (Printbox 4, Bwpprint P0006/0185)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2489-2490 P6-36-8.
  - Gaston County: Dallas: Town Hall (Old Courthouse), circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Flatfile 3, Oimage P0006/0186)
    Johnston number NC2490.
  - Gaston County: Gastonia: Gastonia Public Library, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Printbox 4, Bwpprint P0006/0187)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2475.
  - Gaston County: Mt. Holly: William Rankin House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 2 images (Printbox 4, Bwpprint P0006/0188)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC 2477-2478; Includes two copy negatives.
  - Guilford County: Charles Benbow House (Benbow Tavern), circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 3 images (Printbox 4, Bwpprint P0006/0189)
    NC2951-2952.
  - Guilford County: Gibsonville: Armfield House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 6 images (Printbox 4, Bwpprint P0006/0190)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: 2499-2500.
  - Guilford County: Gibsonville: Sommers House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 2 images (Printbox 4, Bwpprint P0006/0191)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2519.
  - Guilford County: Gibsonville: Sommers Tavern, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 4 images (Printbox 4, Bwpprint P0006/0192)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: 2514, NC2515, NC2517, NC2518.
  - Guilford County: High Point: Haley House/Welch Inn, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 4 images (Printbox 4, Bwpprint P0006/0193)
    Johnston numbers: NC2522-2523; Includes one copy negative.
  - Guilford County: High Point: Springfield Friends Meeting House and Memorial Church, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 4 images (Printbox 4, Bwpprint P0006/0194)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2502-2503.
  - Guilford County: Jamestown: Friends Meeting House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Printbox 4, Bwpprint P0006/0195)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2512.
  - Guilford County: Jamestown: Mendenhall House/Mendenhall Store, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 2 images (Printbox 4, Bwpprint P0006/0196)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2508-2509.
  - Halifax County: Julius Tillery House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 7 images (Printbox 4, Bwpprint P0006/0197)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2567-2571.
  - Halifax County: Julius Tillery House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Flatfile 3, Oimage P0006/0198)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2820.
  - Halifax County: Houses, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 5 images (Printbox 4, Bwpprint P0006/0199)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2530, NC2535-2537, NC2539; Includes original (8x10) negatives.
  - Halifax County: Prospect Hill, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 28 images (Printbox 4, Bwpprint P0006/0200)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2545-2547, NC2549-2553, NC2555, NC2557, NC2557-2558; NC2560-2561; NC2563, NC2565-2566; Includes original (8x10) negatives.
  - Halifax County: Prospect Hill, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 5 images (Flatfile 3, Oimage P0006/0201)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: 2827-2831.
  - Halifax County: Rock House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Printbox 4, Bwpprint P0006/0202)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC3102.
  - Halifax County: Royal White Hart Masonic Lodge, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Printbox 4, Bwpprint P0006/0203)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2534.
  - Halifax County: Airle: Oakland (Thorne Home), circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Printbox 4, Bwpprint P0006/0204)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: 2543.
  - Halifax County: Airle: Williams, Reid, Macon House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 2 images (Printbox 4, Bwpprint P0006/0205)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2528-2529; Includes original (8x10) negatives.
  - Halifax County: Crowells: Benjamin Pope House (ruins), circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Printbox 4, Bwpprint P0006/0206)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2542.
  - Halifax County: Crowells: Benjamin Pope House (ruins), circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Flatfile 3, Oimage P0006/0207)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2886.
  - Halifax County: Crowells: Farm House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Printbox 4, Bwpprint P0006/0208)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2532.
  - Halifax County: Halifax: Clerk of Court's, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 2 images (Printbox 4, Bwpprint P0006/0209)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2540-2541; Include negatives.
  - Halifax County: Halifax: Clerk of Court's, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Flatfile 3, Oimage P0006/0210)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2821.
  - Halifax County: Halifax: Constitution House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Printbox 4, Bwpprint P0006/0211)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2538; Includes original (8x10) negatives.
  - Halifax County: Halifax: Jail, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Printbox 4, Bwpprint P0006/0212)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2533; Includes original (8x10) negatives.
  - Halifax County: Littleton: Little Manor (Mosby Hall), circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 22 images (Printbox 4, Bwpprint P0006/0213)
    NC3074-3077; NC3080, NC3082; NC3083, NC3085; NC3086; NC3089; Includes original negative.
  - Halifax County: Littleton: Little Manor (Mosby Hall), circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 5 images (Flatfile 3, Oimage P0006/0214)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2822-2826.
  - Henderson County: Flat Rock: Pringle House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 4 images (Printbox 4, Bwpprint P0006/0215)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2573-2575.
  - Henderson County: Flat Rock: Saint John in the Wilderness, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Printbox 4, Bwpprint P0006/0216)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2572.
  - Henderson County: Fletcher: Old Tavern (Fletcher House), circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Printbox 4, Bwpprint P0006/0217)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2024.
  - Henderson County: Fletcher: Robert Blake House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 3 images (Printbox 4, Bwpprint P0006/0218)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2022-2023.
  - Henderson County: Rugby: Houses, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 5 images (Printbox 4, Bwpprint P0006/0219)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2025-2028.
  - Hertford County: Murfreesboro: Houses, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Printbox 4, Bwpprint P0006/0220)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2576.
  - Hoke County: Fort Bragg: Long Street Presbyterian Church, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 4 images (Printbox 4, Bwpprint P0006/0221)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2308-2311.
  - Iredell County: Elmwood: Pickney Chambers House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 4 images (Printbox 4, Bwpprint P0006/0222)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2577-NC2579.
  - Iredell County: Elmwood: Waddell House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Printbox 4, Bwpprint P0006/0223)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2583.
  - Iredell County: Mount Mourne: Mount Mourne (Morrison House), circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 3 images (Printbox 4, Bwpprint P0006/0224)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2581.
  - Iredell County: Mount Mourne: Mount Mourne (Morrison House), circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Flatfile 4, Oimage P0006/0225)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2582.
  - Lincoln County: Brevard House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Printbox 5, Bwpprint P0006/0226)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2140.
  - Lincoln County: Burton House (Beattie's Ford Plantation), circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 10 images (Printbox 5, Bwpprint P0006/0227)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2585-2589.
  - Lincoln County: Burton House (Beattie's Ford Plantation), circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 2 images (Flatfile 4, Oimage P0006/0228)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2587.
  - Lincoln County: Catawba River: Riverview (Graham House), circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 7 images (Printbox 5, Bwpprint P0006/0229)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2610-2613.
  - Lincoln County: Catawba River: Riverview (Graham House), circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Flatfile 4, Oimage P0006/0230)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2614.
  - Lincoln County: Denver: Rock Springs Camp Ground, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 2 images (Printbox 5, Bwpprint P0006/0231)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2594-2595.
  - Lincoln County: Iron Station: General Joseph Graham House (Vesuvius), circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 7 images (Printbox 5, Bwpprint P0006/0232)
    NC2625-2629.
  - Lincoln County: Iron Station: General Joseph Graham House (Vesuvius), circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Flatfile 4, Oimage P0006/0233)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2628.
  - Lincoln County: Iron Station: McPelah Presbyterian Church, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Printbox 5, Bwpprint P0006/0234)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2622.
  - Lincoln County: Iron Station: Smith Furnace Office, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Printbox 5, Bwpprint P0006/0235)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2624.
  - Lincoln County: Lincolnton: Hoke House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Printbox 5, Bwpprint P0006/0236)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2615-2616.
  - Lincoln County: Lincolnton: A. Loretz House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 5 images (Printbox 5, Bwpprint P0006/0237)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2614, NC2617-2618, NC2620-2621.
  - Lincoln County: Lincolnton: Ingleside (Forney House), circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 11 images (Printbox 5, Bwpprint P0006/0238)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2598, NC2600, NC2604, NC2605, NC2609.
  - Lincoln County: Lincolnton: Ingleside (Forney House), circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 2 images (Flatfile 4, Oimage P0006/0239)
    NC2608, NC2597.
  - Lincoln County: Lincolnton: Pleasant Retreat Male Academy, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 2 images (Printbox 5, Bwpprint P0006/0240)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2623.
  - McDowell County: Pleasant Gardens, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 5 images (Printbox 5, Bwpprint P0006/0241)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2634-2635, NC2637.
  - McDowell County: Marion: Carson House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 5 images (Printbox 5, Bwpprint P0006/0242)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2630-2632.
  - Mecklenburg County: C.D. Kerns House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 2 images (Printbox 5, Bwpprint P0006/0243)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2657; Includes original (8x10) negatives.
  - Mecklenburg County: Ephraim Davidson House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 2 images (Printbox 5, Bwpprint P0006/0244)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2656.
  - Mecklenburg County: Pitts House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 2 images (Printbox 5, Bwpprint P0006/0245)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2667-2668.
  - Mecklenburg County: Rural Hill Well, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 3 images (Printbox 5, Bwpprint P0006/0246)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2669-2670; Includes original (8x10) negatives.
  - Mecklenburg County: Charlotte: Hezekial Alexander Stone House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Printbox 5, Bwpprint P0006/0247)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2654.
  - Mecklenburg County: Charlotte: Rosedale (Craighead-Davidson House), circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 8 images (Printbox 5, Bwpprint P0006/0248)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2638-2643; Includes original (8x10) negative.
  - Mecklenburg County: Rosedale (Craighead-Davidson House), circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 2 images (Flatfile 4, Oimage P0006/0249)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2911-2912.
  - Mecklenburg County: Ezekiel Wallis House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 2 images (Printbox 5, Bwpprint P0006/0250)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2676, NC2678; Includes original (8x10) negative.
  - Mecklenburg County: Charlotte: Ezekiel Wallis House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Flatfile 4, Oimage P0006/0251)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2910.
  - Mecklenburg County: Charlotte: McIntyre Cabin, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 4 images (Printbox 5, Bwpprint P0006/0252)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2664-2666; Includes original (8x10) negative.
  - Mecklenburg County: Charlotte: Sugaw Creek Presbyterian Church/Academy, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 3 images (Printbox 5, Bwpprint P0006/0253)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2671; Includes original (8x10) negative.
  - Mecklenburg County: Cornelius: Holly Bend (Hollywood), circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 7 images (Printbox 5, Bwpprint P0006/0254)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2659A, NC2660.
  - Mecklenburg County: Cornelius: Holly Bend (Hollywood), circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 2 images (Flatfile 4, Oimage P0006/0255)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2660, NC2662.
  - Mecklenburg County: Davidson: Davidson College Eumanean Hall, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Printbox 5, Bwpprint P0006/0256)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2648; Includes original (8x10) negative.
  - Mecklenburg County: Davidson: Davidson College, Philanthropic Hall, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 2 images (Printbox 5, Bwpprint P0006/0257)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2644; Includes original (8x10) negative.
  - Mecklenburg County: Davidson: Davidson College, Philanthropic Hall, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Flatfile 4, Oimage P0006/0258)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2644.
  - Mecklenburg County: Huntersville: Cedar Grove (Torrence House), circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 4 images (Printbox 5, Bwpprint P0006/0259)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2672-2674; Includes original (8x10) negative.
  - Mecklenburg County: Huntersville: Houses, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Printbox 5, Bwpprint P0006/0260)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2675.
  - Nash County: Aventon: Colonel Alfred Cooper Homestead, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 7 images (Printbox 5, Bwpprint P0006/0261)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2680-NC2684.
  - Nash County: Aventon: Colonel Alfred Cooper Homestead, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Flatfile 4, Oimage P0006/0262)
  - Nash County: Aventon: Lou Burr (Arrington House), circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 6 images (Printbox 5, Bwpprint P0006/0263)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2687-2689.
  - Nash County: Aventon: Lou Burr (Arrington House), circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Flatfile 4, Oimage P0006/0264)
  - Nash County: Aventon: Woodlawn, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 2 images (Printbox 5, Bwpprint P0006/0265)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2707; Includes original (8x10) negative.
  - Nash County: Aventon: Woodlawn, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Flatfile 4, Oimage P0006/0266)
  - Nash County: Nashville: Tories Tavern, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 6 images (Printbox 5, Bwpprint P0006/0267)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2700-2701, NC2703-2704, NC2706.
  - Nash County: Nashville: Tories Tavern, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Flatfile 4, Oimage P0006/0268)
  - Nash County: Rocky Mount: Dortch House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Printbox 5, Bwpprint P0006/0269)
  - Nash County: Rocky Mount: Dortch House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Flatfile 4, Oimage P0006/0270)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2694.
  - Nash County: Rocky Mount: Lewis House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 3 images (Printbox 5, Bwpprint P0006/0271)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2695-2697.
  - Nash County: Rocky Mount: Lewis House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 2 images (Flatfile 4, Oimage P0006/0272)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2695, NC2697.
  - Nash County: Taylors Cross Roads: Breake Farm, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 3 images (Printbox 5, Bwpprint P0006/0273)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2685-NC2686.
  - Nash County: Taylors Cross Roads: Breake Farm, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Flatfile 4, Oimage P0006/0274)
  - Nash County: Wells Crossroads: Wells House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 images (Printbox 5, Bwpprint P0006/0275)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2699.
  - New Hanover County: Wilmington: Bellamy Mansion, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 3 images (Printbox 5, Bwpprint P0006/0276)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2714-2715; Includes original (8x10) negatives.
  - New Hanover County: Wilmington: Burgwin-Wright House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 13 images (Printbox 5, Bwpprint P0006/0277)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2718, NC2721, NC2725, NC2727-2730, NC2733, NC2734, NC2736.
  - New Hanover County: Wilmington: Burgwin-Wright House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 4 images (Flatfile 4, Oimage P0006/0278)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2720, NC2724, NC2731, NC2732.
  - New Hanover County: Wilmington: Darby House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Printbox 5, Bwpprint P0006/0279)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2737; Includes original (8x10) negative.
  - New Hanover County: Wilmington: Governor Edward S. Dudley House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 4 images (Printbox 5, Bwpprint P0006/0280)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2738-2740; NC2742.
  - New Hanover County: Wilmington: Masonic Hall, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 3 images (Printbox 5, Bwpprint P0006/0281)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2746-2747.
  - New Hanover County: Wilmington: Houses, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 8 images (Printbox 5, Bwpprint P0006/0282)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2708-2710; NC2712-2713; NC2748-2750.
  - New Hanover County: Wilmington: Saint James Episcopal Church, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 2 images (Printbox 5, Bwpprint P0006/0283)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2744-2715.
  - New Hanover County: Wilmington: Saint James Episcopal Church, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Flatfile 4, Oimage P0006/0284)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2744.
  - North Hampton County: Jackson: Sheriff's Office and Courthouse, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Printbox 6, Bwpprint P0006/0285)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2751.
  - North Hampton County: Jackson: Sheriff's Office and Courthouse, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Flatfile 4, Oimage P0006/0286)
  - Orange County: Tavern on Ford End Road, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Printbox 6, Bwpprint P0006/0287)
    Johnston number NC277.
  - Orange County: Chapel Hill: Chapel of the Cross, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 5 images (Printbox 6, Bwpprint P0006/0288)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2788; Includes copy negative and original (8x10) negative.
  - Orange County: Chapel Hill: Chapel of the Cross, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Flatfile 4, Oimage P0006/0289)
  - Orange County: Chapel Hill: Old East, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 2 images (Printbox 6, Bwpprint P0006/0290)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2783; Includes copy negative.
  - Orange County: Chapel Hill: Person Hall, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Printbox 6, Bwpprint P0006/0291)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2787.
  - Orange County: Chapel Hill: Samuel Field Phillips House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Printbox 6, Bwpprint P0006/0292)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2774.
  - Orange County: Chapel Hill: Smith Hall (Playmakers Theater), circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 3 images (Printbox 8, Bwpprint P0006/0435)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2790-2791.
  - Orange County: Hillsborough: Ayr Mount (Kirkland House), circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 3 images (Printbox 6, Bwpprint P0006/0293)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2761-2262; Includes copy negatives.
  - Orange County: Hillsborough: Ayr Mount (Kirkland House), circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Flatfile 4, Oimage P0006/0294)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2763.
  - Orange County: Hillsborough: Eagle Masonic Lodge, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 2 images (Printbox 6, Bwpprint P0006/0295)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2766.
  - Orange County: Hillsborough: Gattis House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Printbox 6, Bwpprint P0006/0296)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2755; Includes copy negative.
  - Orange County: Hillsborough: Hazel-Nash House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 3 images (Printbox 6, Bwpprint P0006/0297)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2758-2759; Includes copy negative.
  - Orange County: Hillsborough: Hazel-Nash House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Flatfile 4, Oimage P0006/0298)